Guide to the LAC0018 The James Neff Labor Archives - the IBT Collection, 1953-1989 LAC0018
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Other Organization Publications, 1954-1981; Series 11; 1.5 Linear Feet Box 27, Record Center Box
  - Charting the Course: The Annual Report of the National Catholic Education Association, 1991; Series 11 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Californa AFL-CIO News, 1988; Series 11 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Industrial Relations Research Association Proceedings of the 1961 Spring Meetings, Series 11 (Box 27, Folder 21)
- Constitutions and Conventions, 1901-1981; Series 12; 6 Linear Feet Boxes 28-31,
  This series contains constitutions and convention materials from the International Brotherhood of Teamsters and some of its affiliates, including the International Union of United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink and Distillery Workers. Most constitutions and convention materials are paperback booklets.
  - United Brewery Workers German Language Constitutions, 1901; Series 12 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - United Brewery Workers German Language Constitutions, 1903; Series 12 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - United Brewery Workers German Language Constitutions, 1906; Series 12 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - United Brewery Workers German Language Constitutions, 1908; Series 12 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - United Brewery Workers German Language Constitutions, 1910; Series 12 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - United Brewery Workers German Language Constitutions, 1912; Series 12 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - United Brewery Workers German Language Constitutions, 1914; Series 12 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - United Brewery Workers Constitutions, 1917; Series 12 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - United Brewery Workers Constitutions, 1920; Series 12 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - United Brewery Workers Constitutions, 1923; Series 12 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Local 182 Constitution, 1901; Series 12 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Thirteenth Convention Proceedings, 1935; Series 12 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Fourteenth Convention Proceedings, 1940; Series 12 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - International Conference, 1942; Series 12 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Proceedings of the Fifteenth Convention, 1947; Series 12 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Fifteenth Convention, 1947; Series 12 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Fifteenth Convention Materials, 1947; Series 12 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Brewery Workers Thirtieth Convention, 1948; Series 12 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Taft-Hartley Law Meeting, 1948; Series 12 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Brewery Workers Thirty First Convention, 1950; Series 12 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Proceedings of the Sixteenth Convention, 1952; Series 12 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Sixteenth Convention, 1952; Series 12 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Over the Haul Trade Division Meeting Minutes, 1954; Series 12 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Thirty Fourth Convention, 1956; Series 12 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Brewery Workers Thirty Third Convention Materials, 1954; Series 12 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Seventeenth Convention, 1957; Series 12 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - 17th Convention List of Delegates and Roll Call, 1957; Series 12 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Seventeenth Convention, 1957; Series 12 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Proceedings of the 17th Convention, 1957; Series 12 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Thirty-Fifth Convention, 1959; Series 12 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Brewery Workers Constitution, 1956; Series 12 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Constitution of San Antonio, Texas Convention, 1959; Series 12 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Brewery Worker's Constitution, 1961; Series 12 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Thirty-Sixth Convention, 1961; Series 12 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - 18th Convention Officer Reports, 1961; Series 12 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - 25th Western Conference of Teamsters, 1963; Series 12 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Brewery Worker's Constitution, 1963; Series 12 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Proceedings of the 37th Convention, 1963; Series 12 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Proceedings of the Thirty Eighth Convention, 1965; Series 12 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Constitution of the Cincinnati, Ohio Convention, 1965; Series 12 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - 19th Convention, Miami Beach, 1966; Series 12 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - 19th Convention, 1966; Series 12 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - 19th Convention Officer's Report, 1966; Series 12 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - 39th Convention Proceedings, 1968; Series 12 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - 39th Convention, 1968; Series 12 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - ALA Founding Conference, 1969; Series 12 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Directory of Teamster Locals, 1969; Series 12 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Report "Suburban Affluence: For Whom?", 1969; Series 12 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Manual for Union Organizers, 1970; Series 12 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - National Master Freight Agreement, 1970; Series 12 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Workshop and Trade Division Meeting, 1970; Series 12 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - IBT Proceedings, 1976; Series 12 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Constitution of the Miami Beach, FL Convention, 1971; Series 12 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Proceedings of the 20th Convention, 1971; Series 12 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Teamsters National Bakery Conference, 1971; Series 12 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Constitution of the Miami Beach, FL Convention, 1971; Series 12 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Report on the Fortieth Convention, 1971; Series 12 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Proceedings of the Fortieth Convention, 1971; Series 12 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Proceedings of the Special Convention, 1973; Series 12 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Officers' Report to the 21st Convention, 1976; Series 12 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - How to Write an Union Flyer, 1976; Series 12 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Report on Six Major Corporations, 1977; Series 12 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Report on Five Major Corporation, 1977; Series 12 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - IBT Focus on Negotiations, 1981; Series 12 (Box 31, Folder 19)
- VHS Tapes, 1976-1995; Series 13; 9 Linear Feet Boxes 32-37, All Record Center Boxes
  This series contains various VHS tapes and U-Matic tapes that pertain to the International Brotherhood of Teamsters. Most tapes are directly produced by IBT. Finding aid descriptions are exactly as they are labeled on the tapes. The VHS tapes have been tested for quality and should be in working condition.
  VHS tapes in this series are arranged at random.
  - Window Dub Cam 1 Tape 7 U-Matic Tape, Undated; Series 13 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Window Dub Cam 2 Tapes 1,2 U-Matic Tape, Undated; Series 13 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Window Dub Cam 2 Tapes 3,4 U-Matic Tape, Undated; Series 13 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Window Dub Cam 2 Tapes 5, 6 U-Matic Tape, Undated; Series 13 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Window Dub Cam 2 Tape 7 U-Matic Tape, Undated; Series 13 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Window Dub Cam 3 #1 U-Matic Tape, Undated; Series 13 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - IBT Director of Research Talks about Collective Bargaining Agreements that are Operated in the South and the Impact of those Agreements on your Purchasing Power as Individual Teamsters, Undated; Series 13 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - The Overnight Campaign U-Matic Tape, 1978; Series 13 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - A Public Service Announcement with Ed McMahon on Military Absentee Voting U-Matic Tape, Undated; Series 13 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Arbitration of KBC Brewery vs. XYZ U-Matic Tape, 1981; Series 13 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Window Dub Cam 3 #2, Undated; Series 13 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - The Teamsters Retirees Master #2 U-Matic Tape, 1976; Series 13 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Delta Collage U-Matic Tape, Undated; Series 13 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Paychecks, Prices, Profits, and Prosperity (14:45), Undated; Series 13 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - A Mighty Fine Union (31:08), Undated; Series 13 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Local 100 (31:33), Undated; Series 13 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Labor's Witness (31:17), Undated; Series 13 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - 7th Convention (7:83), Undated; Series 13 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - People, Precincts, and Power (26:16), Undated; Series 13 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - People Politics (28:35), Undated; Series 13 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Central Conference (8:32), Undated; Series 13 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Alec in Wonderland (11:23), Undated; Series 13 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Wonder of Automation (25:17), Undated; Series 13 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Probe James Hoffa (28:59), Undated; Series 13 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Press Conference (7:16), Undated; Series 13 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Dead is Dead (24:57), Undated; Series 13 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Frank Sinatra Spectacular Part 1 (31:10), Undated; Series 13 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Frank Sinatra Spectacular Part 2 (31:24), Undated; Series 13 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Frank Sinatra Spectacular Part 3 (30:00), Undated; Series 13 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Frank Sinatra Spectacular Part 4 (21:56), Undated; Series 13 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Knock on Every Door (28:17), Undated; Series 13 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Together ALF-CIO Part 1 (29:42), Undated; Series 13 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Together AFL-CIO Part 2 (11:12), Undated; Series 13 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - The Inheritance (26:42), Undated; Series 13 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Third Floor (5:35), Undated; Series 13 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - 7th Convention (30:32), Undated; Series 13 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Wages and Prices (14:49), Undated; Series 13 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Meet the Press with J.L.Lewis (29:53), Undated; Series 13 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Robert Coar (21:12), Undated; Series 13 (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Safety Stabilizers (9:38), Undated; Series 13 (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - Cast Me Not Off (28:37), Undated; Series 13 (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - Where Were You? (27:15), Undated; Series 13 (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - Kennedy Speaks to Labor (29:15), Undated; Series 13 (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - The Awesome Servant Part 2 (28:37), Undated; Series 13 (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - Injustice on Trial (18:30), Undated; Series 13 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Labor Committee (14:15), Undated; Series 13 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - DRIVE Campaign Work at IBT with Harding and Zagri (10:00), Undated; Series 13 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Capital Conversation (29:59), Undated; Series 13 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - A Day in the Life of Our Drivers (17:31), Undated; Series 13 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Kennedy's Last Words to Labor (28:24), Undated; Series 13 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Hoffa Interview (10:43), Undated; Series 13 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Are Labor Unions Too Powerful (29:38), Undated; Series 13 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - A Man from Arkansas (26:34), Undated; Series 13 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Vancouver Speech Part 1 (31:00), Undated; Series 13 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Vancouver Speech Part 2 (22:50), Undated; Series 13 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Rails and Roads (29:41), Undated; Series 13 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Civil Rights Statements (5:09), Undated; Series 13 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - T. Children, Luzzo Funeral, Declaration of Principles (7:26), Undated; Series 13 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - San Antonio Interview (8:45), Undated; Series 13 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Hoffa Statement (16:40), Undated; Series 13 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Election: Indiana Teamsters (30:33), Undated; Series 13 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - LBJ Addresses to the 7th AFL-CIO Constitutional Convention (22:54), Undated; Series 13 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - 18th Convention Part 1 (30:21), Undated; Series 13 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - 18th Convention Part 2 (9:25), Undated; Series 13 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Capital Conversation with Syndey Zagri (29:30), Undated; Series 13 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Americans at Work (13:43), Undated; Series 13 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - 1968: Labor's Year of Challenge (14:48), Undated; Series 13 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Castro, Cuba, and Communism Part 1 (30:00), Undated; Series 13 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Castro, Cuba, and Communism Part 2 (24:01), Undated; Series 13 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - DRIVE in Action Part 1 (31:30), Undated; Series 13 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - DRIVE in Action Part 2 (5:04), Undated; Series 13 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - Truck Safety, Safety Hook Up (5:38), Undated; Series 13 (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - The Union Cause (22:55), Undated; Series 13 (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - Hoffa Interview, Oklahoma, 19th Convention (7:58), Undated; Series 13 (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - Teamsters at Work (:30) U-Matic Tape, Undated; Series 13 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - "Turn it Around" Teamster Stewards Solving Problems on the Job (17:00), 1994; Series 13 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - "Teamster Fat Cats" (7:50), 1994; Series 13 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Help Wanted (29:45), Undated; Series 13 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - What's Happened to Sugar? (11:23), ND; Series 13 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - TDU Convention, 1988; Series 13 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Trial By Committee (32:90), Undated; Series 13 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - If People Speak (15:36), Undated; Series 13 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - A State Labor Body (25:39), Undated; Series 13 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - America's Victory: the 1997 UPS Strike (10:00), Undated; Series 13 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Worker Abuse at Overnite Transportation Co. With an Introduction by Rev. Jesse Jackson (IBT), Undated; Series 13 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Actions Speak Louder than Words (22:00), Undated; Series 13 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - It's Your Choice (8:00), 1996; Series 13 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - "No Fast Track" (7:10), Undated; Series 13 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Teamsters on 60 Minutes, Undated; Series 13 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - "A Strong Union Involves Everyone) (7:00), 1995; Series 13 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Ron Cary on Teamster Democrac, Good Morning America (60:00), Undated; Series 13 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Make UPS Deliver (9:00), 1996; Series 13 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Teamsters Speak Out (13:30), Undated; Series 13 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - On the Spot (24:21), Undated; Series 13 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Ship Trainer Demonstrations (9:43), Undated; Series 13 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Diana Kilmury: Teamster (92:00), Undated; Series 13 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Power at Work: Building a Teamster Member-to-Member Action Network (15:00), 1997; Series 13 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - 'What You Say Matters" (15:00), 1996; Series 13 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - On the Road at Overnite (11:00), 1997; Series 13 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Teamsters Update: What's Happening at UPS? (27:00), 1995; Series 13 (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - Buildign Fedex, Building Our Union (9:00), 1997; Series 13 (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - It's Our Contract, We'll Fight for It! (4:00), 1997; Series 13 (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - Teamster Women on the Move (6:00), 1994; Series 13 (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Worker Abuse at Overnite Transportation Co. with an Introduction by Rev. Jesse Jackson (IBT), Undated; Series 13 (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - Better Schools for a Better America (14:05), Undated (Box 36, Item 1)
  - It's Good Business (17:11), Undated (Box 36, Item 2)
  - Beer Belongs (20:42), Undated (Box 36, Item 3)
  - Labor Views News (17:53), Undated (Box 36, Item 4)
  - 17th Convention Miami, Undated (Box 36, Item 5)
  - 7th Convention Part 2 (30:57), Undated (Box 36, Item 6)
  - Cross Exam (25:00), Undated (Box 36, Item 7)
  - Consumers Want to Know (29:50), Undated (Box 36, Item 8)
  - Support Stronger Social Security (9:19), Undated (Box 36, Item 9)
  - Towbridge (12:35), Undated (Box 36, Item 10)
  - Six Golden Kernels (10:30), Undated (Box 36, Item 11)
  - Portland Newspaper (13:00), Undated (Box 36, Item 12)
  - Drive Diner (15:47), Undated (Box 36, Item 13)
  - Brown in the US Senate (2:49), Undated (Box 36, Item 14)
  - The Changing Congress (5:35), Undated (Box 36, Item 15)
  - The Brewester's Heritage (20:11), Undated (Box 36, Item 16)
  - Shur-Guide Stabilizer (8:22), Undated (Box 36, Item 17)
  - The Open Mind (22:13), Undated (Box 36, Item 18)
  - Teamsters Local (11:48), Undated (Box 36, Item 19)
  - Push Buttons and People (21:01), Undated (Box 36, Item 20)
  - Dues and Unions (17:20), Undated (Box 36, Item 21)
  - Labor Views the News (28:37), Undated (Box 36, Item 22)
  - 17th Convention Southern Conference (17:35), Undated (Box 36, Item 23)
  - The Awesome Servant Part 1 (30:23), Undated (Box 36, Item 24)
  - Jackie Presser's Presentation to the Executive Committee U-Matic Tape, 1976 (Box 36, Item 25)
  - Window Dub Cam 1 Tape 3 U-Matic Tape, Undated (Box 37, Item 1)
  - Window Dub Cam 1 Tape 4 U-Matic Tape, Undated (Box 37, Item 2)
  - Window Dub Cam 1 Tape 5 U-Matic Tape, Undated (Box 37, Item 3)
  - Window Dub Cam 1 Tape 6 U-Matic Tape, Undated (Box 37, Item 4)
  - 205 Brewery (11:25), Undated (Box 37, Item 5)
  - American Defense Foundation "Register 2- Paid" #ADP-4 U-Matic Tape, Undated (Box 37, Item 6)
  - Labor's Turning Point, Edited Version, Teamsters Union 1934, Undated (Box 37, Item 7)
  - Jack Presser's Presentation to the Executive Committee re: Retiree's, 1976 (Box 37, Item 8)
  - "Women's Legal Rights PSA" (:30), 1994 (Box 37, Item 9)
  - Trade Problems "IYB #304 Trade Problems" by Grey and Company U-Matic Tape (30:00), 1985 (Box 37, Item 10)
  - Window Dub Cam 1 Tape 2 U-Matic Tape, Undated (Box 37, Item 11)
  - Airline #4, Communications Department, Undated (Box 37, Item 12)
  - 5 Unlabeled U-Matic Tapes, Undated (Box 37, Item 13)
- Photographs, 1950-1989; Series 14; 9 Linear Feet Boxes 38-44, 5 record center boxes and 2 flat boxes
  This series contains various photographs from the International Brotherhood of Teamsters. Some photographs are labeled and have descriptions. Most photos are estimated to be from 1950-1989, with the majority being from the 1950's and 1960's. Photograph types include: contact sheets, mounted photographs, loose photographs, and transparency film slides.
  This series is arranged by photograph format.
  - Contact Sheets, 1950-1989; Series 14 (Box Box 38, Folder 1)
    This box contains unlabeled contact sheets of photographs and mounted photographs. Some mounted photographs are labeled. Estimated dates for the photographs are 1950-1989, with most photographs being from 1950-1970.
  - Contact Sheets, 1950-1989; Series 14 (Box Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Contact Sheets, 1950-1989; Series 14 (Box Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Contact Sheets, 1950-1989; Series 14 (Box Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Contact Sheets, 1950-1989; Series 14 (Box Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Contact Sheets, 1950-1989; Series 14 (Box Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Contact Sheets, 1950-1989; Series 14 (Box Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Contact Sheets, 1950-1989; Series 14 (Box Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Mounted Photographs, 1950-1989; Series 14 (Box Box 39, Folder 1)
    This box contains Teamster mounted photographs, loose photographs, and negatives. Some photographs have descriptions. The estimated photograph dates are 1950-1989, with most photographs being from 1950-1970.
  - Mounted Photographs, 1950-1989; Series 14 (Box Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Mounted Photographs, 1950-1989; Series 14 (Box Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Mounted Photographs, 1950-1989; Series 14 (Box Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Mounted Photographs, 1950-1989; Series 14 (Box Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Loose Photographic Negatives, 1950-1989; Series 14 (Box Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Medium Photographs with Descriptions, 1950-1989; Series 14 (Box Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Medium Photographs with Descriptions, 1950-1989; Series 14 (Box Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Medium Photographs with Descriptions, 1950-1989; Series 14 (Box Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Strike Photos w/ Descriptions, 1950-1989; Series 14 (Box Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Transparency Film Slides, 1950-1969; Series 14 (Box Box 40, Folder 1)
    This box contains transparency film slides having to do with the Teamsters. Slides include photographs and presentation slides. Estimated dates for the slides are 1950-1969.
  - Transparency Film Slides, 1950-1969; Series 14 (Box Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Contact Sheets, 1950-1989; Series 14 (Box Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Transparency Film Slides, 1950-1969; Series 14 (Box Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Transparency Film Slides, 1950-1969; Series 14 (Box Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Transparency Film Slides, 1950-1969; Series 14 (Box Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Transparency Film Slides, 1950-1969; Series 14 (Box Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Transparency Film Slides, 1950-1969; Series 14 (Box Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Transparency Film Slides, 1950-1969; Series 14 (Box Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Contact Sheets, 1950-1989; Series 14 (Box Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Transparency Film Slides, 1950-1969; Series 14 (Box Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Transparency Film Slides, 1950-1969; Series 14 (Box Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Transparency Film Slides, 1950-1969; Series 14 (Box Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Contact Photos, 1950-1989; Series 14 (Box Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Contact Photos, 1950-1989; Series 14 (Box Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Contact Photos, 1950-1989; Series 14 (Box Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Contact Photos, 1950-1989; Series 14 (Box Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Overlarge Mounted Photos, 1950-1989; Series 14 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Overlarge Mounted Photos, 1950-1989; Series 14 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Overlarge Mounted Photos, 1950-1989; Series 14 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Overlarge Mounted Photos, 1950-1989; Series 14 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Overlarge Mounted Photos, 1950-1989; Series 14 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Overlarge Mounted Photos, 1950-1989; Series 14 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Overlarge Mounted Photos, 1950-1989; Series 14 (Box 44, Folder 3)